SUMMARY

Full-stack developer transitioning from Human Resources. Passionate about creating organizational management products as I enjoy seeing thoughts come to life that are productive, efficient, and effective. Over seven years of administrative experience working collaboratively with different teams and handling multiple priorities at once.

SKILLS

LANGUAGES: Javascript, Ruby, HTML, CSS, SQL

FRAMEWORKS & L: NodeJS, ReactJS, Ajax, Express, EJS, jQuery, Twilio, Rails, Bootstrap, ActiveRecord, SASS, React Redux

SYSTEMS & DATABASES: PostgresSQL, Git

TESTING: Jest, Storybook, Cypress, RSpec, Mocha, Chai

SPOKEN LANGUAGES: Fluent English, Conversational Cantonese, Basic Mandarin

PROJECTS

Doable

Dec. 2022

A project management application that makes it easy for a user to organize their new projects/tasks.

Tech Stack: React, Bootstrap, NodeJS, Express, Axios, PostgresSQL

Scheduler

Nov. 2022

A single page client application that uses React view library where a user can book, edit, or cancel interview appointments.

Tech Stack: React, Axios, Classnames, Normalize, Storybook

Double Bubble Trouble

Oct. 2022

A single page application where users can order drinks to pick up. The user and the shop both receive text notification on their orders

Tech Stack: Express, NodeJS, jQuery, SaSS, Twilio, Ajax, PostgreSQL, Bootstrap

EDUCATION

Lighthouse Labs · Sept. 2022 to Dec. 2022

Diploma Full-Stack Web Development

Simon Fraser University · Jan. 2019 to Apr. 2020

Human Resources Management Certificate

University of British Columbia · Sept. 2010 to Apr. 2014

Bachelor of Management 2014

EMPLOYMENT

Provincial Health Services Authority

Labour Relations Coordinator · Nov. 2020 to June 2022 · Vancouver, BC

- Supported the Labour Relations team with letters, grievance responses, reports, minutes and other ad hoc related requests
- SuperUser in Human Resources Solutions: manage all users (new employees/union members, etc.) and grievances, familiar with PeopleSoft to query employee information

Bureau Veritas Commodities Canada

Human Resources Assistant · June 2019 to Apr. 2020 · Vancouver

- Provided Human Resources support to the Regional HR Manager for over 300 employees
- Utilized SAP SuccessFactors and ADP WorkForce Now to process all HR-related data